Finding Aid for Stanley S. Kresge Papers 1909-1985
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs
    The Photographs subseries is arranged in five sequences: Kresge Company/K mart Corporation; Kresge Foundation; Kresge, Sebastian and Clara; Personal; and Miscellaneous. The series is one-half linear foot, and each sequence is arranged topically.
    - Kresge Company/K mart Corporation
      - Annual Arts and Crafts Show (5th annual) undated (Reel 20)
      - Fiftieth Anniversary (Folder UAm)
      - Headquarters (Reel 20)
        (includes slide)
      - Officers (Reel 20)
      - Stockholders Meetings (Reel 20)
      - Stores and Warehouses, 2 folders (Reel 20)
        (includes visits by Sebastian and Stanley; store opening in Baltimore, Md.)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 20)
    - Kresge Foundation
      - Buildings (built with Kresge Foundation grants) (Reel 20)
      - Headquarters (Reel 20)
      - Trustees (Reel 20)
    - Kresge, Sebastian and Clara
      - General (Reel 20)
      - Ninetieth Birthday (Reel 20)
      - Portraits (Reel 20)
    - Personal
      - Albion College (Reel 20)
      - Ceremonies (Reel 20)
      - Fiftieth Wedding Anniversary (Reel 20)
      - Graham, Billy (Reel 20)
        (Stanley and Dorothy with Graham, or attending Graham events)
      - Interlochen National Music Camp: Kresge Organ (Reel 20)
      - Maine (Reel 20)
      - Mustard Seed (Reel 20)
      - Portraits (Stanley only) (Reel 20)
      - University of Michigan (fraternity house) (Reel 20)
    - Miscellaneous (Reel 20)
  - Films, all 16 mm, silent
    The Films subseries contains eight 16 mm reels of black and white, and color films. The content is of football and baseball games.
    - 1930 Michigan-Illinois football, "Mother in her 1880 blue dress", b&w (Box 11)
    - 1932 World Series; Michigan-Northwestern football, b&w (Reel 11)
    - 1940 Michigan-Pennsylvania football, 2 reels; color (Reel 11)
    - 1943 Michigan-Notre Dame football, 2 reels; color and b&w (Reel 11)
    - 1946 Michigan-Army football, 2 reels; color